http://www.holylandmall.net/privacy.html

Holy Land MallAll CategoriesChristian Merchandise Israel Merchandise Gary Rosenthal Collection Gifts from Israel Privacy Statement SHIPPING SECURITY Wholesale
Links Share Holy land Yellow pages Inspirational Wristbands YouTube - ISRAEL
Christian MerchandiseJewish MerchandiseIsrael MerchandiseGary Rosenthal CollectionDead Sea Cosmetic ProductsJerusalem ArtVIDEO/VHS/DVDSOFTWAREMUSICBOOKSJEWELRYGifts from IsraelPrivacy StatementSHIPPINGSECURITYWholesale Links ShareHoly land Yellow pagesInspirational WristbandsYouTube - ISRAELIDF SHOPMessianic Gifts from Israelview cartHome > Privacy StatementPrivacy StatementThis site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo!
hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically
collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate.
If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically
collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the Yahoo!
Privacy Policy for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information.
This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for www.holylandmall.net.Information Collection and UseHoly Land Mall is the sole owner of the information collected on this site.
We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.OrderWe request information from the user on our order form.
Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date).
This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer’s orders.
If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.LinksThis web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we Holy Land Mall are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.
We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.
This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
Log FilesWe use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.
IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.Home | about us | privacy policy | send email | site map | view cartCopyright 2019 Your store name here. All rights reserved.
